A Guide to the Harry Emilius Stocker Collection Sermons & Manuscripts 1909-1929
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
{Special Collections, University of Virginia Library}
Harry Emilius Stocker Collection Sermons & Manuscripts 1909-1929
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11497
There are 450 items.
The collection consists chiefly of sermons by Stocker arranged according to the church year.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift: Arthur F. Stocker, Charlottesville, Va., April 12, 1999.
Scope and Content
The collection consists chiefly of sermons by Stocker arranged according to the church year.
The collection also contains some religious and travel articles by him, including articles for The Moravian; his book reviews of Harry Emerson Fosdick's Adventurous Religion and Samuel M. Shoemaker's Children of the Second Birth; and "A Short History of the International Order of the King's Daughters and Sons 1886-1924" by Clara Morehouse.
Contents List
- Articles, chiefly by Harry Emilius Stocker 1919-1929 (Box 1)
  includes "A Short History of the [International Order of King's Daughters and Sons] 1886-1924" by Clara Morehouse
- Articles in The Moravian by Harry Emilius Stocker 1911-1929, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Book Reviews by Harry Emilius Stocker [ca. 1926-1927] (Box 1)
- Sermons by Harry Emilus Stocker, with Table of Contents ca. 1909-1914, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Sermons by Harry Emilius Stocker--Miscellaneous ca. 1915-1918, n.d. (Box 1)
- Sermons by Harry Emilius Stocker--Church Seasons and Other Sermons (I), with Table of Contents 1922, n.d. (Box 1)
- Sermons by Harry Emilius Stocker--Church Seasons and Other Sermons (II), with Table of Contents n.d. (Box 1)
- Sermons by Harry Emilius Stocker--Church Seasons, with Table of Contents 1924, n.d. (Box 1)
- Sermons by Harry Emilius Stocker re Missions ca. 1913, n.d. (Box 2)
- Sermons by Harry Emilius Stocker, Table of Contents n.d., 4 folders (Box 2)
- Sermons by Harry Emilius Stocker ca. 1927-1929, n.d., 3 folders (Box 2)